Hello everyone
Welcome to my cloakroom
What should I wear to a party later?
There are too many clothes and I don’t know which one to choose.
Since it's a party, let's wear a dress
I’ll choose these shoes and a bag too.
May I ask who it is?
it's me
It should be my boyfriend Tom who is here
Then I have to prepare quickly
Tom, give me five minutes
What do you think of me?
Magic Mirror, Magic Mirror, who is the most beautiful person in the world?
Do you still need to ask?
Of course it's your mother
Don't bully my daughter
But…
Yeli, the more I look at her, the more she looks like you.
Isn’t the boss usually like dad?
when i was pregnant
But I beg God desperately
Please, she must be like me, not like her dad
Right, Yeli?
What's wrong with you?
We were returned
Box No. 6?
Right
What do you want to say about wanting to meet former female stars?
It's basically Aoke
Those guys are very knowledgeable.
Meiling
Yeah, sister
Yili
Yeli, come and play with your sister.
Don't
I don't want to play with ugly sisters
Someone as beautiful as your mother
There are many adults vying to play with her
Yeli needs to be sensible, you know?
82097…
do this with me do this with me
From that day on, Yeli’s mother
I never went back to the store again.
She decided to devote all her efforts to cultivating her daughter
Let her be the center of attention
so beautiful
Your face looks big in the camera
Learn from mom
Tuck your chin in
The corners of the mouth are slightly raised
Very good That's it
keep it
Keep shooting
strike a pose
Very good very beautiful
[Actor audition]
stop
Zhu Yili
Aren't you angry with other children?
More photogenic and prettier than you on screen?
I haven't eaten in three days
If you don't eat, you will really be so hungry that you faint.
bring it
Hurry up
The audition is over and you’ll be chosen before you eat.
If I'm chosen, it's because I have to film a movie
Will you not let me eat again?
Memorize the script well
I saw it all
The way you looked when you failed the exam and came out
During this time, you have been relying on your mother's relationship.
You just got through it, right?
A person without strength
Just by helping my parents...
No, I only rely on my parents for support...
What's so great
mom
That day…
Yeli finally knew
The secret to successful auditions on your own
And her real life experience
Why haven't you gotten in the car yet?
Mom, the zipper on the back of the skirt is not closed.
Children should sit in the back seat
I will definitely pass the audition anyway
Don't worry, I won't tell dad
I'm hungry. I want to eat sweet and sour pork.
From that day on
Yeli gave up her career as a child star
Zhu Yili
what's the matter with you
Mom, it seems it’s time for me to get a new mobile phone.
I used to take advantage of my mother’s unbearable secret
Yeli who got benefits in exchange
Ironically, since then
He also began to resort to any means necessary
Hide your own secrets
Magic mirror, magic mirror
In this world…
Who is the most beautiful person?
Even if it's all lies
Uncle, how much does this cost?
[Dear Mom and Dad, Happy 20th Wedding Anniversary]
What day is today?
[Daejundong Valet Delivery Service]
Of course, the job of collecting scandals about others
Can't relax either
[I want to report]
Who knows if it will be used someday?
["Good-natured Competition"]
good morning
Uncle, you know
I'm not good at studying
So everyone looks down on me
i know
But what if I'm good at reading?
It’s not like you can make a lot of money just by knowing how to read.
There's something about me that's better than others
I'm particularly keen on the smell of money
Are you looking for Sister Jina?
Everyone thought she was hiding and preparing to retake the exam
But things don't seem that simple
Even Jay doesn’t know, right?
I knew my uncle and I would be able to chat
I've felt this way for a long time
If he was really missing, why didn't you call the police?
There must be something inside that cannot be told.
Of course I'm not interested in this kind of thing
It’s just that I’m not a reliable person with my mouth.
If you want to shut my mouth
It is best to use diamond or pure gold locks
It has to be heavy enough to lock
I just mentioned it casually
Yeli, are you short of money recently?
But will taking the money once solve the problem?
As long as you don't reject it
I can support you for a long time
Of course, the money will not be given to you for free
You have to pay something too
what do you want me to do
This is it
I have to think again...
what can you do for me
But…
You are more beautiful without makeup
Today we invite the dean of J Medical Center
Dr. Liu Taijun, who is also a gastrointestinal surgeon
Hello Dr. Liu
Hello
your latest book
"Dajundong Dad's Healthy Plan for Perfect Score in the Big Exam"
Attracted by many people
In recent years, teenage patients who have come to me
Significantly more
Because I sit and read for a long time
cause indigestion
Constipation, gastroesophageal reflux, etc.
Various gastrointestinal diseases emerge in endlessly
I heard you also have two at home
Daughter preparing for exam
Yes
As a father and a doctor
Of course I also think about what kind of diet
Most helpful to candidates
From now on there will be no instructions from me
Even if there is an order, we are not allowed to ship it.
I can't give it to you today
Please help me
[During on-campus examinations
Neighboring residents please forgive me and cooperate to lower the volume]
All the students here take medicine just to stay up late studying
Even just look at the test questions given by the cram school
Come
Put everything away
Hold head with hands
There are three exam papers in total this time
Start passing exam papers
Pass it on
OK start the exam
[Math 3-1 Midterm Exam]
I was originally ranked 20th in the school
It's all your fault that I fell off the list
do you know
[Third Grade 1st Place Yu Seqi & Liu Jieyi]
Too ridiculous
[Hunter]
Seulgi, long time no see.
You look back
please
Don't wave here, people will see you
Are you still so difficult to get along with?
What time will you finish school today?
Just look at your quiz scores
I didn't expect you to be so powerful
how did you do it
teacher
Please…
Can I skip the health check-up?
why
Health check-up is a benefit only available to the top 20 students in the school
Do you have any special reason?
No...no...
nothing
This is not a check you can do if you have money.
And you are number one in the school
Although the results have not been officially logged into the system,
Teacher, choice 5 for this question should be considered correct, right?
Didn't you say that the answer to this question is controversial?
deputy squad leader
Ranked third in the first test
I can understand that you must be very uncomfortable
But you should be more serious before the exam
What's the use of remediating it now?
Okay, everyone, go back
Abominable
[J Medical Center]
Who was that man at the school gate just now?
Is it your boyfriend?
what
OK
I'll pretend I didn't see it
health check
you do it
Me?
What about you?
why don't you do it
I do it every year
Let people who have never tried it try it out
I can still have more time to study
Maybe I can get first place too
I should still ask Seulgi to teach me.
How to get first place in the exam
Cui Jing
Thanks
Cui Jing I love you
See the transcript on the bulletin board
Do you know how happy I am?
Our Seulgi is too strong
Directly dominate Jiangnan
When I first saw you, I knew you were not simple.
Will I finally have friends who go to Korean universities?
Who said I am your friend?
Hello
Why should people of the same origin be so indifferent?
I am originally from Seoul
Sure enough, people still have to hang out in big cities
Seoul is great
The level is just different
If you have something to say, please tell me
I still want to go back to study
Oh
Look at your hard work
I will definitely be admitted to a Korean university
Okay, I'm convinced
Why is it so expensive?
Speaking of which, do people here know?
You are a drug addict from a kindergarten
You have to pick up the goods this time by yourself.
Or find someone to buy it from
I quit after I transferred to another school.
Get first place in the school
Still in school in Jiangnan
You also said you didn't take any medicine
All the students here take medicine
Who told me that in the first place?
This one should suit you very well
Do you want to try it on?
Was it you who encouraged Xiuzhen?
where is she now
Cui Xiuzhen
What happened to her?
First give back the medicine you stole
With the money for that medicine, I can buy this dress.
Excuse me, is this one available in size 105?
Sir, No. 105 will not be restocked until next week.
Hey, did you hear?
It won't be available until next week
Hey, you used to steal medicine
I turned a blind eye
How many times have I let you go
Don’t you think you should return a favor to me?
You have to have some conscience
I've been poor since I was a kid
There is no such thing as conscience
What a rude bitch.
See you next week
Let’s meet with a smile then
[J Medical Center]
The friendship in Caihua Girls’ High School is so superficial
How much money did they spend on cram school?
As a result, you, a person without tutoring,
But he got the first place in the school
Of course they will be jealous
It sounds like you are different from them
I want to take the music major
Not like those nerds
Ranking is more important than life
At what time will the physical examination end?
Is your mom coming to Parents Night tonight?
No, I didn't tell her
me too
My parents are in Paris
So I didn't tell them on purpose.
Afraid of disturbing their work
Lest they fly back all the way
Bus to Cairo
Please fasten your seat belt
[J Medical Center Shuttle Bus]
[Treatment Room Pharmacy Room]
Please take off all clothes except underwear
Change into examination clothes before coming out
[Parents’ medical history]
I have to take extra classes at night. I don’t want to feel groggy.
I want to have a test without anesthesia
Do you usually take any medicine?
Do you have sexual experience?
Pregnancy or miscarriage experience
Please also fill it in
Doesn't this constitute an invasion of privacy?
Why do we need to ask these questions during the physical examination?
Are you still having trouble sleeping recently?
Yes
How
did you do anything bad
I have what you need most right now
Do you want to come and get it?
After passing the examination room, turn right
Leave the physical examination area and go up to the lobby on the first floor.
[pharmacy room]
Go to the corridor to the pharmacy
You will see an elevator dedicated to medical staff
[pharmacy room]
Take that elevator
Go up to the top floor and enter the door
You can't come in here
not there
go out
[Roof stairs]
There is an escape ladder at the end of the corridor
Go up there and hide on the top floor
I'll call you again
Get up and I'll take you to a place
You won't refuse my kindness anymore, will you?
Because you are admirable
you finally found it
Not hard to find, right?
I'm so stupid
Uniforms, cram school and midterm exams…
These are all the means you use to make me surrender.
I resisted stupidly
what do you want from me
I'm willing to do anything
what do i want from you
You need the settlement letter from my dad's medical lawsuit?
I can…
Get it for you
But…
You have to help me too
Really?
But reconciliation…
It's what I least want
What do you want, Seulgi?
I want to live a stable life
Jay, you won’t understand
I have been bullied and trampled on
How did you survive?
If you want to survive, you can only study
Studying is the only way to protect me
Is my only protective umbrella
So please make sure that my physical examination results are okay.
I must be admitted to the Department of Medicine of Korea University
Live your life peacefully...
I've been helping you
It's the same now, isn't it?
Let’s celebrate today first
You might think that just by taking medicine
You can get the first place in Caihua Girls' High School
but not like that
That’s why I won’t sell you medicine
Yu Seqi
Liu Jieyi
See our names tied for the top spot
It feels so exciting
If it had been anyone else, I would have been very unhappy
But because it’s you…
I'm very happy
Then keep your promise and answer me
Why don't you answer me?
If this midterm exam
If you do better than me, I'll tell you
How did I get your basic information?
And why should we get it?